

Address

1/874A Mount Eden Road, Three Kings, Auckland

Mobile 0211027873

Email rkdgusdn9@gmail.com

GitHub github.com/rkdgusdn9

LinkedIn https://www.linkedin.com/in/bennykang

Carrier Objective

Highly motivated graduate majoring in Software Development with Network & Security as minor from Auckland University of Technology. I aim to broaden my experience and skills in software development and Information security, in an organization that values their people and encourages personal development.

Key Strengths

React + Typescript

- Currently working on making a fitness web application using React with Typescript,
 SASS
- · Functional components based

IoT, C++ and Cloud Development

- Worked on IoT software development projects during a summer internship at Datacom which predominantly utilised several sensors, Arduino machine, Microsoft IoT Central, C++ and Microsoft Azure Developer Tools
- Had an experience with Kanban methodology

C#, Web and Mobile Development with Database

- Worked on Xamarin mobile software development project during R&D internship at Business Mechanix for both front-end and back-end with a database
- Had an experience with SCRUM methodology

Team player, Communicates Effectively and Takes Initiative

- Communicated with the Integration team, the business consultants, the project manager and the team lead to work efficiently together
- Took the initiative to pitch our project to supervisors and managers while some technical difficulties were being handled by the other members. The whole team was commended for excellent team work and having a great flow for our presentation
- Bilingual (Korean, English)

Problem Solving by hard working and patience

 The client needed to clean the code for Arduino C++ which they were not able to get it done.

Took extra time to work and research after working hours and was able to clean the code and even finished the other wish-list items.

Ended up getting the greatest feedback from the client.

Passion for Technology and Innovation

 Constantly attends hackathons and industry-related presentations and training events

Education

Auckland University of Technology, New Zealand – Bachelor of Computer and Information Science (BCIS), Software Development, 2015 – 2018

Major papers taken

- Program Design and Construction
- Software Engineering
- Web Development

- Software Development Practice
- Research and Development Project
- IT Project Management

Microsoft Student Accelerator - Microsoft, 2018 - 2019

Completed the Microsoft Student Accelerator programme that provides soft skills and entrepreneurship training as well as experience with leading edge technologies to students that are put into practice by facilitation work placement with partner companies.

New Zealand School of Tour and Tourism, New Zealand – Business Management Diploma Level 5, 2012 – 2013

- · National Diploma in Business Management
- One of top three performing students
- Member of the student council

Work Experience

Software Developer Intern at Datacom Group LTD, Auckland, New Zealand December 2018 – March 2019

- Worked on Internet of Things project for Vulcan Steel
- Used IoT Central to visualise data, Azure functions to create a workflow by Microsoft and C++ code with Arduino machine
- Kanban methodology
- Sent measured voltage, on/off status of client's working machine from IoT Central to Storage table.

Software Developer Intern at Business Mechanix LTD, Auckland, New Zealand March 2017 - November 2017

- Worked as both Software Developer and SCRUM Master
- Scrum methodology
- Worked on validation check function, local-cashing, SQL server and web API using .NET C# (Xamarin).
- Used Team Foundation Server for source controlling

General Manager at BannSang restaurant, New Zealand January 2013 – July 2014

- Worked as General Manager
- In charge of hiring people, ordering raw ingredients, serving customers and alcohol licensing.

Others